{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163028463","data":{"timestamp":" 947163028463"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163033593","data":{"timestamp":" 947163033593"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163039036","data":{"timestamp":" 947163039036"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163067074","data":{"timestamp":" 947163067074"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 7ddf2f1f-cae1-4472-b56e-98720a3b19e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_724_412-724-597"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 724"," userResponse":" 724"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163081820","data":{"timestamp":" 947163081819"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 7ddf2f1f-cae1-4472-b56e-98720a3b19e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_715_840-715-893"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 715"," userResponse":" 715"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163098352","data":{"timestamp":" 947163098352"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 7ddf2f1f-cae1-4472-b56e-98720a3b19e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_559_603-622-559"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 559"," userResponse":" 559"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163110335","data":{"timestamp":" 947163110335"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 7ddf2f1f-cae1-4472-b56e-98720a3b19e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_496_496-576-524"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 496"," userResponse":" 496"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163137106","data":{"timestamp":" 947163137106"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 7ddf2f1f-cae1-4472-b56e-98720a3b19e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_799_609-879-799"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 799"," userResponse":" 799"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163184996","data":{"timestamp":" 947163184996"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 7ddf2f1f-cae1-4472-b56e-98720a3b19e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_760_760-794-594"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 760"," userResponse":" 794"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163194725","data":{"timestamp":" 947163194725"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 7ddf2f1f-cae1-4472-b56e-98720a3b19e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_760_760-794-594"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 760"," userResponse":" 760"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163226456","data":{"timestamp":" 947163226456"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 7ddf2f1f-cae1-4472-b56e-98720a3b19e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_449_696-449-538"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 449"," userResponse":" 449"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163288172","data":{"timestamp":" 947163288172"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 7ddf2f1f-cae1-4472-b56e-98720a3b19e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_909_713-875-909"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 909"," userResponse":" 875"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163297138","data":{"timestamp":" 947163297138"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 7ddf2f1f-cae1-4472-b56e-98720a3b19e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_909_713-875-909"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 909"," userResponse":" 909"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163338024","data":{"timestamp":" 947163338024"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 7ddf2f1f-cae1-4472-b56e-98720a3b19e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_441_441-477-677"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 441"," userResponse":" 441"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163380070","data":{"timestamp":" 947163380070"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 7ddf2f1f-cae1-4472-b56e-98720a3b19e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_874_552-874-510"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 874"," userResponse":" 874"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163389501","data":{"timestamp":" 947163389499"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 7ddf2f1f-cae1-4472-b56e-98720a3b19e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_874_552-874-510"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163395479","data":{"timestamp":" 947163395479"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 7ddf2f1f-cae1-4472-b56e-98720a3b19e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL4.decr.93"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_874_552-874-510"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163404579","data":{"timestamp":" 947163404578"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" ebbbeac5-d5d0-40f0-a93c-9854d329c815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163404816","data":{"timestamp":" 947163404815"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" ebbbeac5-d5d0-40f0-a93c-9854d329c815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163405792","data":{"timestamp":" 947163405791"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" ebbbeac5-d5d0-40f0-a93c-9854d329c815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163407076","data":{"timestamp":" 947163407075"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" ebbbeac5-d5d0-40f0-a93c-9854d329c815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163410027","data":{"timestamp":" 947163410026"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" ebbbeac5-d5d0-40f0-a93c-9854d329c815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163410880","data":{"timestamp":" 947163410879"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" ebbbeac5-d5d0-40f0-a93c-9854d329c815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163411203","data":{"timestamp":" 947163411202"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" ebbbeac5-d5d0-40f0-a93c-9854d329c815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163412446","data":{"timestamp":" 947163412446"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" ebbbeac5-d5d0-40f0-a93c-9854d329c815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163416002","data":{"timestamp":" 947163416001"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" ebbbeac5-d5d0-40f0-a93c-9854d329c815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163416991","data":{"timestamp":" 947163416990"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" ebbbeac5-d5d0-40f0-a93c-9854d329c815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163417253","data":{"timestamp":" 947163417252"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" ebbbeac5-d5d0-40f0-a93c-9854d329c815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163418215","data":{"timestamp":" 947163418215"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" ebbbeac5-d5d0-40f0-a93c-9854d329c815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163421136","data":{"timestamp":" 947163421136"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" ebbbeac5-d5d0-40f0-a93c-9854d329c815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163422180","data":{"timestamp":" 947163422179"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" ebbbeac5-d5d0-40f0-a93c-9854d329c815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163422660","data":{"timestamp":" 947163422660"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" ebbbeac5-d5d0-40f0-a93c-9854d329c815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163423517","data":{"timestamp":" 947163423516"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" ebbbeac5-d5d0-40f0-a93c-9854d329c815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163423586","data":{"timestamp":" 947163423586"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" ebbbeac5-d5d0-40f0-a93c-9854d329c815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163429321","data":{"timestamp":" 947163429321"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" ebbbeac5-d5d0-40f0-a93c-9854d329c815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:60..960.off100.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163476082","data":{"timestamp":" 947163476081"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" ebbbeac5-d5d0-40f0-a93c-9854d329c815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163481118","data":{"timestamp":" 947163481118"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" ebbbeac5-d5d0-40f0-a93c-9854d329c815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163490300","data":{"timestamp":" 947163490299"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 0942ae8d-b153-4dd0-912a-d9651c7e2704"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163490535","data":{"timestamp":" 947163490534"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 0942ae8d-b153-4dd0-912a-d9651c7e2704"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163491509","data":{"timestamp":" 947163491508"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 0942ae8d-b153-4dd0-912a-d9651c7e2704"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163492797","data":{"timestamp":" 947163492796"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 0942ae8d-b153-4dd0-912a-d9651c7e2704"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163495760","data":{"timestamp":" 947163495759"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 0942ae8d-b153-4dd0-912a-d9651c7e2704"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163496617","data":{"timestamp":" 947163496616"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 0942ae8d-b153-4dd0-912a-d9651c7e2704"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163496935","data":{"timestamp":" 947163496934"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 0942ae8d-b153-4dd0-912a-d9651c7e2704"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163498180","data":{"timestamp":" 947163498180"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 0942ae8d-b153-4dd0-912a-d9651c7e2704"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163501752","data":{"timestamp":" 947163501751"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 0942ae8d-b153-4dd0-912a-d9651c7e2704"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163502743","data":{"timestamp":" 947163502743"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 0942ae8d-b153-4dd0-912a-d9651c7e2704"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163503006","data":{"timestamp":" 947163503005"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 0942ae8d-b153-4dd0-912a-d9651c7e2704"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163503960","data":{"timestamp":" 947163503959"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 0942ae8d-b153-4dd0-912a-d9651c7e2704"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163506852","data":{"timestamp":" 947163506851"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 0942ae8d-b153-4dd0-912a-d9651c7e2704"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163507893","data":{"timestamp":" 947163507893"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 0942ae8d-b153-4dd0-912a-d9651c7e2704"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163508378","data":{"timestamp":" 947163508376"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 0942ae8d-b153-4dd0-912a-d9651c7e2704"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163512959","data":{"timestamp":" 947163512959"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 0942ae8d-b153-4dd0-912a-d9651c7e2704"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163513032","data":{"timestamp":" 947163513032"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 0942ae8d-b153-4dd0-912a-d9651c7e2704"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163518142","data":{"timestamp":" 947163518142"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 0942ae8d-b153-4dd0-912a-d9651c7e2704"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163575849","data":{"timestamp":" 947163575849"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 1678d20a-80ab-401f-a09d-a61673a9a9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_665_665-517-902"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 665"," userResponse":" 665"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163586967","data":{"timestamp":" 947163586967"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 1678d20a-80ab-401f-a09d-a61673a9a9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_806_730-806-567"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 806"," userResponse":" 730"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163595860","data":{"timestamp":" 947163595860"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 1678d20a-80ab-401f-a09d-a61673a9a9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_806_730-806-567"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 806"," userResponse":" 806"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163671868","data":{"timestamp":" 947163671868"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 1678d20a-80ab-401f-a09d-a61673a9a9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_774_558-508-774"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 774"," userResponse":" 508"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163689967","data":{"timestamp":" 947163689966"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 1678d20a-80ab-401f-a09d-a61673a9a9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_774_558-508-774"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 774"," userResponse":" 774"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163721681","data":{"timestamp":" 947163721680"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 1678d20a-80ab-401f-a09d-a61673a9a9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_657_657-826-693"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 657"," userResponse":" 657"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163806460","data":{"timestamp":" 947163806460"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 1678d20a-80ab-401f-a09d-a61673a9a9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_677_865-435-677"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 677"," userResponse":" 677"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163849593","data":{"timestamp":" 947163849593"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 1678d20a-80ab-401f-a09d-a61673a9a9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_723_730-723-668"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 723"," userResponse":" 730"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163858446","data":{"timestamp":" 947163858446"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 1678d20a-80ab-401f-a09d-a61673a9a9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_723_730-723-668"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 723"," userResponse":" 723"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163888560","data":{"timestamp":" 947163888560"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 1678d20a-80ab-401f-a09d-a61673a9a9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_542_459-542-551"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 542"," userResponse":" 459"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163898359","data":{"timestamp":" 947163898359"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 1678d20a-80ab-401f-a09d-a61673a9a9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_542_459-542-551"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 542"," userResponse":" 542"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163916996","data":{"timestamp":" 947163916995"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 1678d20a-80ab-401f-a09d-a61673a9a9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_728_728-770-459"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 728"," userResponse":" 770"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163925378","data":{"timestamp":" 947163925378"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 1678d20a-80ab-401f-a09d-a61673a9a9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_728_728-770-459"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 728"," userResponse":" 728"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163954600","data":{"timestamp":" 947163954600"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 1678d20a-80ab-401f-a09d-a61673a9a9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_926_533-926-719"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 926"," userResponse":" 926"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163973109","data":{"timestamp":" 947163973109"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 1678d20a-80ab-401f-a09d-a61673a9a9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_509_500-509-495"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 509"," userResponse":" 500"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163983028","data":{"timestamp":" 947163983028"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 1678d20a-80ab-401f-a09d-a61673a9a9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_509_500-509-495"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 509"," userResponse":" 495"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947163992374","data":{"timestamp":" 947163992373"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 1678d20a-80ab-401f-a09d-a61673a9a9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_509_500-509-495"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 509"," userResponse":" 509"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947164000861","data":{"timestamp":" 947164000861"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 1678d20a-80ab-401f-a09d-a61673a9a9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_509_500-509-495"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947164005614","data":{"timestamp":" 947164005614"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 1678d20a-80ab-401f-a09d-a61673a9a9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_509_500-509-495"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947164010861","data":{"timestamp":" 947164010861"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 1678d20a-80ab-401f-a09d-a61673a9a9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_509_500-509-495"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947164017119","data":{"timestamp":" 947164017118"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" 1678d20a-80ab-401f-a09d-a61673a9a9be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_509_500-509-495"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947164085261","data":{"timestamp":" 947164085260"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" bf102541-5864-4c99-826c-484ccec7117c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_706_776-553-706"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 706"," userResponse":" 776"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947164094082","data":{"timestamp":" 947164094082"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" bf102541-5864-4c99-826c-484ccec7117c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_706_776-553-706"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 706"," userResponse":" 706"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947164114888","data":{"timestamp":" 947164114888"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" bf102541-5864-4c99-826c-484ccec7117c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_665_665-517-902"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 665"," userResponse":" 665"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947164133412","data":{"timestamp":" 947164133412"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" bf102541-5864-4c99-826c-484ccec7117c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_657_657-826-693"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 657"," userResponse":" 657"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947164146497","data":{"timestamp":" 947164146497"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" bf102541-5864-4c99-826c-484ccec7117c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_728_728-770-459"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 728"," userResponse":" 770"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947164154445","data":{"timestamp":" 947164154445"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" bf102541-5864-4c99-826c-484ccec7117c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_728_728-770-459"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 728"," userResponse":" 728"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947164172671","data":{"timestamp":" 947164172671"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" bf102541-5864-4c99-826c-484ccec7117c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_537_537-667-825"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 537"," userResponse":" 537"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947164183040","data":{"timestamp":" 947164183040"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000106_154944"," gameId":" bf102541-5864-4c99-826c-484ccec7117c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_400..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF10-BL3.decr.94"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_777_777-682-539"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 777"," userResponse":" 539"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}